-Hey!
-Hi!
(Penny:)I thought you went to the comic book
store on Wednesdays.
(Leonard:)Yeah, but Sheldon and Amy
were having date night
(Leonard:)and they don't need me there
to make it awkward.
(Leonard:)They have each other for that.
(Leonard:)So, how was school?
(Penny:)Oh, good. Check it out.
(Penny:)The Disappointing Child
by Beverly Hofstadter. Oh!
(Leonard:)-You bought my mom's book?
-Yeah!
(Penny:)It's on the recommended reading list
for my psychology class.
Oh!
(Leonard:)Come on. Not that book.
(Leonard:)It's got, like, every horrible story
from my childhood in it.
(Penny:)Oh, cool. Are there pictures?
Seriously, please End another book.
(Penny:)Oh, come on. Why?
How bad could it be?